question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The term &quot;Spam&quot; came before the food product &quot;Spam&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                      "question": "NCIS stands for &quot;Navy Corps Investigative Service&quot;",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                       "question": "Adolf Hitler was born in Australia. ", "correct_answer": "False",
                                       "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Spoon theory is a theory, utilizing &quot;Spoons&quot; as a metaphor for energy they can use in a day.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "&quot;Number 16 Bus Shelter&quot; was a child&#039;s name that was approved by the New Zealand government.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "The commercial UK channel ITV stands for &quot;International Television&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "An eggplant is a vegetable.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
